Vivienne Dickie

07773713517 | vdickie31@gmail.com

12 Killynure Wood Tempo Road, Enniskillen, BT746FR, Co. Fermanagh

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an experienced catering manager, who is organised, conscientious and driven to meet targets and financial budgets. I can manage and motivate a team to achieve results and meet the needs of customers. I am a flexible and positive person and I can problem solve, making effective decisions to achieve deadlines. I am self motivated, approachable and open minded to new ideas. I have an eye for attention to detail to meet high expectations. I am practical and have a hands on approach to work. I have excellent communication and listening skills in dealing with staff and customers. I am trustworthy and I have a calm and efficient approach to my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aramark

Catering Manager

11/2010 - Present

Responsibilities & Achievements

My key responsibilities are the daily management of food service staff, front of house and counter displays to the required company standards, weekly HACCP audits, weekly online ordering with nominated suppliers, completion of weekly online accounts and forecast reports, daily cash management, weekly lodgements and monthly stocktakes.

Completion of monthly online staff payroll, online staff training in relation to food safety and health and safety and

job inductions. As and when required covering cash till operation and cooking in the event of staff absence.

My main achievements over the past 8 years working in Aramark are successfully managing and achieving company budgetary targets and building and retaining a motivated team of staff.

Dunnes Stores Enniskillen

Cafe Manager 05/2007 - 10/2009

Responsibilities & Achievements

I was responsible the daily management of food services, staff, front of house and counter displays to the required store standards. Weekly HACCP audits, weekly ordering with nominated suppliers, completion of weekly accounts and monthly stocktakes. Completion of weekly staff rotas, daily cash till

1/2

operation, cooking as and when required.

QUALIFICATIONS

Enniskillen Collegiate Grammar School

1975 - 1982

GCSE

English Language (B), English Literature (C), Mathematics (C), History (C), Biology (C), French (B), Home Economics (B)

A Level

Home Economics (B), English Literature (C)

REFERENCES

References are available on request

2/2